{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "Your boss wants you to give him some work by the end of the day. You need more time. You ask: '___ I give it to you tomorrow?'\n",
            "a": "Could",
            "b": "Would",
            "c": "Should",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "22",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't think the government ___ a main road through our village.\n",
            "a": "must build",
            "b": "might build",
            "c": "should build",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "22",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tom ___ the CDs from the shop. That was a bad thing to do.\n",
            "a": "shouldn't have stolen",
            "b": "mustn't have stolen",
            "c": "shouldn't be stealing",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "22",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "It's time ___ the winner of the award for best actress. The winner is â€“ Laura Mitchell!\n",
            "a": "I announce",
            "b": "I should announce",
            "c": "to announce",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "22",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "It's time ___ next month's meetings. We need to send out the programme soon.\n",
            "a": "we plan",
            "b": "for us to plan",
            "c": "we must plan",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "22",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "There's nothing to do at home. I ___ go for a walk.\n",
            "a": "might as well",
            "b": "can't",
            "c": "needn't",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "22",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don't leave your glasses on the chair. Someone ___ sit on them.\n",
            "a": "should",
            "b": "may",
            "c": "must",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "22",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you're a member of the sports centre, you _________ pay to use the tennis courts. They're free to members.\n",
            "a": "can't",
            "b": "mustn't",
            "c": "don't have to",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "22",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "___ know a lot about animals for this job?\n",
            "a": "Are you able to",
            "b": "Could you",
            "c": "Do you have to",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "22",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You _________ eat a lot just before you go swimming. If you do, you might feel ill.\n",
            "a": "mustn't",
            "b": "don't have to",
            "c": "needn't",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "22",
            "type": "2"
        }
    ]
}